https://mbssecurities.com/privacy-policy/

U.S. Agency Bonds
Certificates of Deposit (CD)
Mortgage-Backed Securities
Collateralized Mortgage Obligations (CMO)
U.S. Agency Bonds
Certificates of Deposit (CD)
Mortgage-Backed Securities
Collateralized Mortgage Obligations (CMO)
Privacy Policy
Multi-Bank Securities, Inc. (MBS) respects your right to privacy. We are committed to securing the confidentiality and integrity of your personal information. We are proud of our privacy practices and want our current and prospective clients to understand what information we collect and how we use it.
Why We Collect Your Information
We gather your information about you and your accounts so we can (1) know who you are and thereby prevent unauthorized access to your information, (2) design and improve the products and services we offer and (3) comply with the laws and regulations that govern the financial industry.
What Information We Collect
We may collect the following types of nonpublic personal information about you:
Information about your identity, such as your name, address and Taxpayer Identification Number.
Information about your transactions with us.
Information we receive from you from applications, forms or direct discussions with you.
Sources From Which We Obtain Your Information
We collect nonpublic personal information about MBS’s clients from the following sources:
Information we receive from you from applications, forms or direct discussions with you.
Information we may obtain via the internet.
Information we receive from our clearing firm or any third-party vendor for authentication purposes.
What Information We Disclose
Your securities account is carried by our clearing firm pursuant to clearing agreements. We may disclose to them all the information we collect regarding your account. Our clearing firm is contractually obligated to keep the information we have provided them confidential and use the information only for the services required and as allowed by applicable law or regulation.
We also may disclose some nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to facilitate servicing your account or to our regulators upon proper request, except as permitted by law and noted above. Moreover, we will not release information about our customers or former customers, except as noted above, unless one of the following conditions is met:
We receive your prior written consent.
We believe the recipient to be you or your authorized representative.
We are required by law or regulation to release information to the recipient.
Confidentiality and Security
We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal account information. We also restrict access to your personal and financial data to authorized associates who have a need for these records. We require all non-affiliated organizations to conform to our privacy standards and are contractually obligated to keep the provided information confidential and used only as requested. Furthermore, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices described in this notice even after your account is closed or becomes inactive.
The examples contained within the Privacy Policy are illustrations and are not intended to be exclusive. If there are material changes to this policy, they will be posted on our website at www.mbssecurities.com.
About Us
Overview
Veteran-Owned Business
Community Involvement
Management
History
Services
Strategic Alliances
U.S. Agency Bonds
Certificates of Deposit (CD)
Mortgage-Backed Securities
Collateralized Mortgage Obligations (CMO)
Corporate Notes and Bonds
Commercial Paper
Municipal Bonds
Community Reinvestment Act (CRA)-Eligible Investments
Community Impact Mortgage-Backed Securities Program
Funding
Overview
Online Features
MBS Form CRS
For institutional investors only. Not intended for the investing public. Copyright © 2020,
Multi-Bank Securities, Inc. Member of FINRA & SIPC; MSRB Registered. All rights reserved. Click here to get to FINRA BrokerCheck. Multi-Bank Securities, Inc. is not a chartered bank or trust company, or depository institution. It is not authorized to accept deposits or trust accounts and is not licensed or regulated by any state or federal banking authority.
